<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NickNames</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="nicknames_the_game">NickNames The Game</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How To Play</string>
    <string name="submit_how_many_players_are_going_to_join_the_game_below">Submit how many players are going to join the game below :</string>
    <string name="insert_number_here">Insert number</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="now_submit_your_real_name_and_the_nickname_you_want_to_play_with">Submit your username and nickname you want to play with.</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="insert_real_name_here">Insert username</string>
    <string name="insert_nickname_here">Insert nickname</string>
    <string name="mothernicknames">"Mother" have to submit 2 more nicknames.</string>
    <string name="the_game_has_started">The game has started.</string>
    <string name="randomize">Randomize</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="player_nicknames">Players with their Nicknames:</string>
    <string name="leaderboard">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="scoreboard">Scoreboard</string>
    <string name="next_round">Next Round</string>
    <string name="_2_point">Add 2 points</string>
    <string name="_1_point">Add 1 point</string>
    <string name="start_timer">Start timer</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="game_score_board">Game Score Board : </string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="end_round">End Round</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_leader_board">LeaderBoard</string>
    <string name="hide_hint">Hide hint</string>
    <string name="show_hint">Show hint</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change language</string>
    <string name="choose_lang">Choose language :</string>
    <string name="some_nicks">Some nicknames :</string>
    <string name="plz_insert_nick">Please insert a nickname</string>
    <string name="mother_is">The mother is :</string>
    <string name="plz_inster_both">Please insert both username and nickname</string>
    <string name="the_name">The name :</string>
    <string name="already_exists">already exists, username must be unique</string>
    <string name="wow_dup_nick">Wow duplicate nickname that\'s rare! Put another nickname for the game to progress</string>
    <string name="give_phon_mother">Now give the device to the mother and the game begins, have fun !</string>
    <string name="submited_pass_phon">" submitted his nickname, pass the phone to "</string>
    <string name="mother_has_2_more">Mother has to submit 2 more nicknames</string>
    <string name="the_nickname">The nickname :</string>
    <string name="added_success">" added successfully"</string>
    <string name="the_game_starts">They game shall now start</string>
    <string name="pass_to_next_player"> submitted his nickname successfully, pass the phone to the next player</string>
    <string name="read_aloud_3_times">Read the nicknames aloud 3 times :</string>
    <string name="name_arrow_score">( Name ----> Score )</string>
    <string name="rules">Welcome to Nicknames: The Game!\nNumber of players: 3–10.\nPurpose of the game: Become the first player to collect 3 points.\n
        \nQuick instructions !\n
        \n\t1st Step : Enter the number of players.\n
        \n\t2οnd Step : Each player puts his name (saved in the application) and a nickname.\n
        \n\t3rd Step : The application selects the mother, which adds 2 more nicknames and reads all the nicknames.\n
        \n\t4th Step : One player starts and asks someone else a nickname, if he finds his nickname then they become a team and the other learns the nickname of the first, otherwise the player who was asked does not take a turn until one player is left alone or there are 2 teams.\n
        \n\t5th Step : The team that was created last has the opportunity to win; the timer starts and one of its players has to say all the nicknames and who they belong to. Each team has 3 chances, if they do not succeed, the mother wins (gets 1 point). If a team wins, members get 1 point or 2 if there is only one. \n
        \n\t6th Step : The game ends when someone has 3 points.\n
        \n
        \nThorough instructions :\n
        \nPreparation: Enter a number of players. Then, each player individually enters in the application his name and nickname. Then the \"mother\" is randomly selected, who must then select 2 more nicknames. From this point until the end of the round the mother handles the application. After all the nicknames have been chosen, the mother must read aloud and slowly all the nicknames (of the players and her own) in random and different order each time without referring to the players to whom correspond to the pseudonyms. \n
        The game begins! \n
        4–10 Players: The player sitting to the right of the mother plays first. This player is trying to guess the nickname of any other player he wants (except the mother). If the 2 players find it, they become a team. The player whose nickname remains hidden whispers it to his teammate. Now they make all the decisions together. This team is guessing again. If the nickname is not found correctly, then nothing happens and the player who was asked must in return guess the nickname of a player(he can ask the same person). If a team finds the nickname of a player who is not in a team, this player joins the team and the other members whisper their hidden nickname. Still, if one team guesses the other\'s hidden nickname, the teams merge. When there are now only two teams (regardless of individual, for example, a player can be a team on his own and all other players can be the other team) the final phase of the round begins. Each team chooses its leader. The team with the fewest members starts (in case of an equal number, the team that was formed first starts) and has certain time to hold a meeting. When this time has passed the leader must correctly say ALL the pseudonyms and the persons to which they correspond (of his team, of the opposing team and of the mother). If the leader finds them, his team gets 1 point and the game progresses to the next round (in case the team consists of only one player, he gets 2 points). If the leader doesn\'t guess everything right, the mother says out loud that she has made a mistake and in turn the other group tries to find all the nicknames. Each group has 3 chances to find all the nicknames correctly. In case no team finds them, the mother gets 1 point and the game progresses to the next round.\n
        3 Players: The process is the same as above, with the difference that the group creation phase is omitted, and the 2 players (the third is the mother) proceed directly to the last phase, where everyone tries to find the nickname of their opponent and the mother\'s 3 nicknames</string>
    <string name="three_mothernicks"> has nicknames :</string>
    <string name="name_to_add_points_to">Please insert a valid username to add points</string>
    <string name="point_added_to">Point\\s added to :</string>
    <string name="winner_s_is_are">Winner(s) :</string>
    <string name="game_scoreboard">Game scoreboard :</string>
    <string name="insert_number_before_submitting">Please insert number before submitting</string>
    <string name="three_to_ten_ppl">The game is played with 3 to 10 people</string>


</resources>
